clicknloan.com 2013-10-26

# Privacy Policy - ClickNLoan

ClickNLoan.com (“ **ClickNLoan** “) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the ClickNLoan.com website (the “ **Website** “). ClickNLoan created this privacy policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** “) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.

This Privacy Policy applies whether you are accessing the Website via a personal computer, a mobile device or any other technology or devices now known or hereafter developed or discovered. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any websites owned by ClickNLoan’s parent companies, subsidiaries or affiliates or other third-parties (collectively, “ **Third-Party Websites** “), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.  For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT: (1) YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD, A RESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES, AND ARE OTHERWISE LEGALLY QUALIFIED TO ENTER INTO AND FORM CONTRACTS UNDER APPLICABLE LAW; AND (2)  YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.

Each time you use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time you used the Website.  For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.

### 1\. U.S. GOVERNING LAW

The Website is designed and targeted to U.S. audiences and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U.S. ClickNLoan makes no representation that this Website is operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of, or governed by, other nations.

If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the U.S., you access and use the Website at your own risk and initiative and you, not us, are responsible for compliance with any applicable local and national laws. By using the Website and/or providing us with your Personal Information (as defined in Section 3(e), below), you: (1) consent to the transfers and processing of any Personal Information you provide to the Website; (2) acknowledge that U.S. law provides a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of various countries including, but not limited to, the European Union; and (3) understand that the Website will deal with your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and U.S. law. CONSEQUENTLY, YOU HEREBY WAIVE ANY CLAIMS THAT MAY ARISE UNDER THE LAWS AND REGULATIONS THAT APPLY TO YOU IN OR OF ANY OTHER COUNTRY OR JURISDICTION.

### 2\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

ClickNLoan does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If ClickNLoan obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, ClickNLoan will immediately delete such information from its database. Because ClickNLoan does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, ClickNLoan has no such information to use or disclose to third parties.

### 3\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

**(a)   Traffic Data.  **Like most website operators, ClickNLoan automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) Internet Protocol (IP) addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website; and (v) full Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) click stream data, including referring URLs, date and time, and content viewed or searched for on the Website (collectively “ **Traffic Data** “).  Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you.

**(b)  Cookies. **A “ **Cookie** ” is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website.  The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website.  ClickNLoan uses “session” cookies to collect information about your use of the Website and to give you a more personalized browsing experience and help you navigate the Website more efficiently from page to page. These cookies are temporary and are deleted when you close your browser. ClickNLoan uses “persistent” cookies to gather statistical information about repeat usage from your computer or workstation. For additional information on ClickNLoan’ uses of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies and Web Beacons, below.

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES.  IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

**(c)  Web Beacons. **“ **Web Beacons** ” (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access Cookies. Unlike Cookies which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, Web Beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages (or in e-mail). Web Beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. For additional information on ClickNLoan’ uses of Web Beacons, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies & Web Beacons, below.

**(d)  Ad Serving. **ClickNLoan uses third-parties for advertising and analytics for pages that we host. These third-parties may place Cookies on your machine, use Web Beacons, gather Personal Information, gather IP addresses and log data to collect traffic and activity data in order to deliver relevant metrics, content, and advertising. The collection of this information by third-parties are subject to such third-parties’ privacy policies.  For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.

**(e)  Personal Information.** During the loan application process, you will be asked to provide ClickNLoan certain information that personally identifies you (“ **Personal Information** “). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) “ **Identity/Contact Data** ” (such as your name, address, and email address); and (2) “ **Demographic Data** ” (such as your birthday, city/town, zip code, state, credit, and military status). In each case, you will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Website will not gather it surreptitiously. ClickNLoan may supplement the Personal Information you provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies, third-party service providers, etc.) who may lawfully provide such information to ClickNLoan.

### 4\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES

**(a) Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies and Web Beacons**

ClickNLoan analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons to help ClickNLoan better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, ClickNLoan is able to better design the Website to improve your experience, and to serve you more relevant and interesting content and advertisements.  From time to time, ClickNLoan may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. ClickNLoan does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies or Web Beacons to Personal Information.  
**(b)  Personal Information**  
(i) **Generally.** ClickNLoan uses your Personal Information and to identify you, to confirm facts about you, to send you information about ClickNLoan and ClickNLoan’ products and services, and to contact you when necessary in connection with your use of the website. ClickNLoan uses your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons, from time to time ClickNLoan may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.  
(ii)  **Disclosure Practices.** Except under the following circumstances, ClickNLoan will keep your Personal Information private, and will not sell or otherwise share it with third parties:

  * **Disclosure to Parent Companies, Subsidiaries and Affiliates.** ClickNLoan discloses Personal Information to its parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates for marketing and/or administrative purposes.

  * **Disclosure to Lenders.** ClickNLoan refers consumers to lenders who provide loans. ClickNLoan discloses Personal Information to Lenders, who use your Personal Information to identify you, to confirm facts about you, to deliver financial products and services to you, to help assess requests for financial products and services, and as necessary to service your loan.

  * **Marketing Communications.** ClickNLoan provides your Personal Information to third parties, so that they may contact you directly, online and offline, with information about additional products and services (“ **Marketing Communications** “).  You may opt-out of having your Personal Information provided to third parties for the purpose of Marketing Communications by clicking [here](http://www.optout-blgl.net/o-lglb-c11-d78ec46a9b45bb143e83500f6709101d) and following the opt-out instructions. **** Even after opting-out, you may continue to receive Marketing Communications from third parties to whom ClickNLoan has already has provided your Personal Information. You will be responsible for contacting those third parties directly to request that you receive no further Marketing Communications.

  * **Disclosure in Connection with Services.   **ClickNLoan discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide Services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as ad serving (see Section 2(d), above), email management, hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security.

#### **By Law or to Protect Rights.**   ClickNLoan discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when ClickNLoan believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ClickNLoan, third parties or the public at large.

  * **Business Transfers; Bankruptcy.** ClickNLoan reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of ClickNLoan’ assets.  Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it.  Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by ClickNLoan’ successor organization.

### 5\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law (CA Civil Code § 1798.83), California residents who provide personal information to businesses in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to either: (1) a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided; or (2) to be notified of a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. ClickNLoan has elected the second option. To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, click [here](http://www.optout-blgl.net/o-lglb-c11-d78ec46a9b45bb143e83500f6709101d) and follow the opt-out instructions.

### 6\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

ClickNLoan has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of your Personal Information.

### 7\. EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS; MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

By completing an application through the Website, you consent to receive certain administrative email communications from ClickNLoan. You also consent to receive periodic online and offline marketing communications from ClickNLoan. You may opt-out of receiving ClickNLoan marketing communications at any time by clicking [here](http://www.optout-blgl.net/o-lglb-c11-d78ec46a9b45bb143e83500f6709101d) and following the opt-out instructions.

### 8\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

You represent and warrant that all information you provide on any application form or otherwise in connection with your use of the Website will be complete and accurate. You cannot update or delete previously submitted information. In the event that your information changes after you have submitted an application through the Website, you must submit a new application with your new or updated information.

### 9\. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

ClickNLoan neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites.  Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by ClickNLoan. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect your privacy.

### 10\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ClickNLoan reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. Each time you use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply.  Accordingly, each time you use the Website you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time you used the Website.  Unless ClickNLoan obtains your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.

**Effective Date:** November 2012
